Creating personas in marketing,
在营销中创建用户画像
you just imagine what Becky would like and what she wears,
想象一下 Becky 喜欢什么 她穿什么
and where she shops, and why she would want to be a customer of your company.
她在哪里购物 以及为什么她想购买你公司的产品
The way that we do it is we actually take real lead files from the client.
我们这样做的方式 实际上就是从客户端获取真实的潜在客户资料
We do analysis using LinkedIn data.
接下来 我们会使用 LinkedIn 数据进行分析
This is their age, this is their title.
这是他们的年龄 这是他们的职位
We create personas for the client that are based on real data.
我们为客户创建基于真实数据的用户画像
My name is Emily Peters.
我叫 Emily Peters
I'm a brand strategist and I'm founder of Uncommon Bold.
我是一名品牌策略顾问 也是 Uncommon Bold 的创始人
Uncommon Bold is a brand strategy studio.
Uncommon Bold 是一个品牌战略工作室
We help companies when they feel like they're misunderstood.
当客户感到茫然无措时 我们会帮助他们
We do a bunch of analysis and then we help them to choose
我们会做很多分析 然后帮他们选定
the direction that they want to go and hopefully to
他们想要在哪个方面改进
create something that's really easily understood,
我们也希望做出一些非常容易理解 非常令人信服的东西
really compelling and is going to help them get a ton of VC money,
从而帮助他们获得大量的风投资金
a ton of press, a ton of people to join their company.
大量的新闻关注 并吸引大量的人才加入他们的公司
My clients are all doctors and scientists and engineers,
我的客户中 有医生 科学家 工程师
and they all think in data.
他们都习惯通过数据思考问题
The way I do a very detailed data analysis with
我通过媒体报道对我的客户进行非常详细的数据分析
media coverage for my clients to give them a sense of the quality of the coverage,
而我让他们了解的是 媒体覆盖的质量
not just the quantity they're receiving.
不仅仅是数量
So we created an algorithm, really simple,
所以我们创建了一个算法 不仅用起来非常简单
that helps to show,
而且有助于展示
create a score that they can measure month over month to see how they're doing.
得出一个他们可以按月测算的分数 看到每个月的情况如何
When I first developed that,
我第一次开发它的时候
it was pretty transformational to have this very simple formula that was very
那时候 这个非常简单的公式 是相当具有变革性的
easy to understand but that nobody had ever used before.
它很容易理解 但之前从没有人使用过
I actually posted it on my website and a lot of other people use it now.
我当时是在我的网站上发布的 很多人现在还在使用它
So that's nice to know that I'm helping
知道我正在帮助
other people to demonstrate the value of their work.
其他人展示他们工作的价值 这是一件很愉快的事
Everything needs to be managed and measured.
一切都需要管理和衡量
With data, you can actually go back and look at the numbers,
有了数据后 你其实可以回过头来查看数字
look at the traction,
看一看客户影响力
you can really get in there with a client and have tough conversations with them
你可以与客户一起对这些数字进行深入探讨
because of using real information versus just opinion.
要注意的是 我们这里要使用的是真实信息 而不仅仅是你的意见
You can get pretty far in your career without data.
没有数据 你也可以在职业生涯中走得很远
But, if you have a good sense of how to put
但是 如果你懂得
together a compelling slide or a compelling graph,
如何使用数据让你的幻灯片或图表更具有可信度
it elevates your ability to really convince
你的说服力就会大大提升
other people to take the course of action you want to have.
即 能够更好地说服别人采取你想要的行动方案